[Episode 12]
Do it lightly! He'll wake up.
Okay, I got it.
Anyways, is Uncle really mad at us?
Yeah, because we kept asking him
not to go to Australia,
he got annoyed with us.
He said we annoy him?
Wouldn't you be annoyed?
Always making him mad and stuff.
I don't do that anymore!
I won't make him mad from now on.
Good. You better be good from now on.
Why don't you be good yourself, stupid?
Shhh! Uncle might wake up!
It'll be all your fault if Uncle runs away.
I'm sorry. I was wrong.
You make me so angry.
I'll be good from now on
so he doesn't go to Australia.
Find a replacement immediately.
Seeing his face is torture.
Who are you?
I'm Mr. Choi Yun's manager.
I'm Choi Yun's manager.
Mr. Kang told me I start work today.
Is something wrong?
I should at least say goodbye.
Eunchae.
Eunchae. Eunchae.
Eunchae!
Eunchae?
Mr. Cha? What's wrong with her?
- I'm not sure.
- What?
What were you doing neglecting her
to the brink of death?
What?
Are other people's lives not as important as your son's?
My gosh.
Get out of the way!
Where's the doctor?
What's the problem?
She's got a fever from stress.
We'll alleviate her fever first since it's too high.
Nurse, get the fever medication.
Why is that bastard here again?
Who are you talking about?
Mr. Cha! Cha Muhyeok, that jerk!
Didn't Mr. Kang tell you? Can't you get the job done?
- Maybe no one told him yet.
- Then inform him right now!
What did he just say to me? Who does he think he is?
- Where is Mr. Cha?
- ER...
He's in the ER with Eunchae.
Eunchae is sick.
What?
Sorry. I'm sorry, but
I told her to go home,
but she kept insisting that
she wanted to be with Yun.
Anyways.
There's something going on between
Muhyeok and Eunchae, right?
Something feels off.
Cha Muhyeok has a crush on Eunchae, maybe?
Am I right?
Don't tell Eunchae about Muhyeok.
Don't ever tell Eunchae that Muhyeok is dying.
Muhyeok.
Can I talk to you?
- Hey, Yun!
- Muhyeok.
- Yun!
Yun!
Yun! Yun!
Help!
Yun, are you okay?
- I'm going to kill him.
- Calm down.
I'm really going to kill him. Don't stop me.
I'll definitely kill him today, that jerk.
Even if you don't kill him...
He'll die soon anyway.
Even if you don't kill him,
he's dying anyway. Don't do it.
What are you talking about?
Are you okay, Blockhead?
You scared me! I thought you were gonna die!
Eunchae.
If I do one good thing before I die,
maybe I won't go to hell.
And it will be good for you, Yun, and Yun's mom.
I'll never forget your kindness as long as I live.
Is that your way of life?
You'll sacrifice your own daughter
for the sake of Yun?
Is that what you think?
Didn't you hear her moaning
from being sick from exhaustion?
Watch what you're saying, Mr. Cha.
Were you always so loyal?
You're like a dog.
Doing as your master tells you to do.
Are you just going in to change?
Yeah.
Mr. Song.
Yes?
What I'm about to say right now...
Just listen. Don't take it the wrong way.
Okay.
Well, I don't care what you think of it.
You can even throw a rock at me.
I'd gladly be stabbed for it, even. For saying this...
About Mr. Cha.
There's no way of helping him?
Is he just waiting to die?
That's what I heard.
Then if he's going to die...
Could he help Yun before he dies?
What?
I know saying this is a sin, but...
I've asked Mr. Kang for Mr. Cha's health records.
Detailed diagnostic analysis is
needed to be sure, but...
Fortunately, he has the same blood type as Yun.
What do you mean?
If he can save Yun...
I can give him anything he wants.
I'll even give him my entire fortune.
The body will become dirt after he dies anyway.
I told you. You can throw rocks at me.
What a horrible person I am!
I said I'd gladly let you kill me!
I'll take any sort of punishment!
Mom.
Galchi!
Kim Galchi!
Yes?
How do I look? Handsome?
Yes.
Am I hotter than the singer Choi Yun?
Is Choi Yun hotter?
Blockhead! Good morning.
You're okay. You're okay.
You're okay.
You're okay, right, Eunchae?
This one.
Wow. It's so pretty.
I'll take this one.
It's for my son's engagement. Please wrap it nicely.
And let's see that one as well.
- This one?
- Yes.
You asked for it to be served in the ice cream?
Mom! You've watched too many movies!
Oh, yeah. You are an actress.
Okay.
Thank you, Mom. Love you.
Did you wait long?
You must be hungry.
Eunchae.
I wanna eat something delicious.
Hospital food isn't so bad if you learn to enjoy it.
Let's go outside. I want some fresh air.
You shouldn't go outside.
I'll be more sick by being in this bed every day.
Just this once.
Yes. I got everything.
I'm going down right now.
You're still here?
Mr. Kang...
Said to keep showing up for work...
Leave these with me.
And go get breastfed by your mom some more,
you baby.
But...
- Get going.
- Yes?
Get going!
Yes.
Are you sure you're okay?
I'll be fine.
As long as you're with me, I'll be okay.
That little new manager left
to be breastfed by his mom.
When he's old enough, I'll give him the position.
Where are you two going?
♪ Everyone lives like that since they are so tired ♪
♪ They live like they are dead ♪
♪ In a world where dying is better than living, oh no ♪
♪ Wringing the heart like wet laundry ♪
♪ I want to throw away in water
this body, nose and throat ♪
♪ They live like they are dead
thanks to music and magazines ♪
Mr. Song.
Come here. Do you think it will fit her?
Who?
Muhyeok's sister. The slow girl.
Do you think it will look good on her?
I'm just trying to be nice.
It's just that I accused her by mistake.
I feel sorry, so I was going to apologize.
I'll take all these.
Yes, ma'am.
I bought some fish, beef,
and fruits at the grocery store.
Can you load them into the car?
It's not for any favors.
I'm just going to simply apologize.
Apologize. An apology.
You know what an apology is, don't you?
I've to go to the bathroom. Wait for me inside.
Okay.
What can you do for Eunchae?
What can you do for her?
If it were me,
if I thought I couldn't do anything
for the girl I loved,
I would give her up.
I think that's being a real man.
I'm going to propose to Eunchae today.
What's wrong with this?
Can you do this for me?
Why? Wanna kill me?
If I were that easy to kill, I'd have died long ago.
This color sucks.
It sucks.
♪ You are the only woman for me ♪
♪ I miss you constantly, you're only for me ♪
♪ You're the light of my life ♪
♪ You shed light on my dark and empty world ♪
♪ I haven't even been able to buy you clothes or
hold your now rough hands ♪
♪ Please, can you forgive me ♪
♪ I'm sorry you had to meet someone like me ♪
Yun! Yun!
Yun!
Are you okay?
Yun! Yun!
What am I going to do?
Aren't you going to help me with this?
You're the worst ever.
I told you I came to apologize. Stop judging me.
Why can't you just take it for what it is?
Fine. Fine. You're so good.
And I'm such a bad witch who deserves to be stoned.
And you're the moral-rich Buddha.
I got my ticket to hell. You go on to heaven.
Yes. You'll go to heaven!
Are you really not going to help me?
Why do they live in such a poor area?
There's not even a road!
Making me suffer.
I've been treating him too nicely.
A servant should only be treated as a servant.
If we weren't going to be in-laws, why I'd...
Where on earth is building 16-1?
So what gifts do you want from Santa?
I want dolls, shoes, clothes, and snacks.
How about you, Galchi?
I want Uncle.
Uncle?
Yes, I hope Santa tells Uncle not to go to Australia.
Me, too.
I want Uncle instead of clothes and shoes.
Uncle said he's going to Australia?
Don't worry.
Since Galchi was good, Santa will tell him to stay.
I'm not a kid.
I know there's no Santa.
No. Santa exists, stupid.
Excuse me.
I'm so tired.
I guess I found the place.
How have you been?
Who are you?
Don't I look familiar?
Yes.
I'm the mother of singer Choi Yun.
You saw me a lot on TV, right?
Choi Yun visited us before as well.
Really? Yun was here?
Tell her to go home.
Tell that lady to go home.
What's wrong, Mom? Don't be rude to your elders.
About what happened last time... I'm really sorry.
I came to apologize.
I'm sorry, okay?
Tell her to go away.
Miss.
Miss, I'm really sorry.
Miss! Miss!
I beg you.
I'm begging you. Forgive me.
I'm really sorry. Forgive me.
Yun! Yun!
No chance, Muhyeok.
You don't stand a chance against me.
I'm different than you.
I have a chance, unlike you.
I'm not as desperate as you are.
I know you're running your mouth
because you're embarrassed,
but shut up. You're wearing me out!
Do you think I'm a joke?
Or you think this is funny?
Why are you acting like this?
Because he's too weak to retaliate?
Is that why you're being so rude?
Because he's too weak to even lift a finger?
You shouldn't do that to Yun.
How important can a girl be? How important can I be?
Yun liked you so much.
How can you betray him like this?
That goes for you and me both!
Don't come here again.
Get lost, Mister.
Please get out of my life.
I beg you.
So? Do you like it?
Pretty, right?
Wanna try these on?
Wow, so pretty.
So pretty!
What do you think? Isn't your mom pretty?
Really pretty, right?
Yes, like a princess.
Kid, you have great taste!
What was your name again?
Galchi. Kim Galchi.
Galchi? What a special name!
Galchi is a special name to me, too.
I can't eat a meal without galchi fish.
I named him...
What?
Galchi. I named him.
You did? What a cool mother.
Ms. Cha.
You have such a pretty smile.
Your smile reminds me of...
Have we met before?
Now that I look closely,
your eyes, nose, and lips.
They look so familiar.
I'm not sure why but I feel
my eyes welling up with tears.
Weird. I want to cry. Why would that be?
[Audrey's Tale of 3 Babies]
[Picture of twins when they were born]
Why? Why would the baby die?
Where is he?
Bring my baby here right now, Mom.
How would I bring it back from the dead?
[Witness to the shocking tale of Cha Muhyeok and
Yun Seo-kyeong, twins famous actress Audrey abandoned]
Truth will prevail in the end.
What goes around comes around.
What brings you here?
So pretty.
Mr. Cha.
Mr. Cha. You're back.
Uncle!
Uncle, the lady bought me
clothes, shoes, hat, and a ring!
I came to apologize to your sister
about what happened last time.
I know it's a little late, but I felt so bad about it.
I'm here to apologize. I'm really sorry.
She even brought us fuel for the furnace and
bought lots of beef, fruits, and food for us to eat.
It's getting so late. I should get going.
I heard you were sick.
I brought some vitamins and supplements.
Be sure to take them three times a day.
You were right, Mr. Cha.
My child's life is just as important
as the lives of others.
You were right, Mr. Cha.
I think I was crazy because of my child.
When a mother is blinded by her child,
she can't see the difference between right and wrong.
A mother can be blinded by a child.
Mr. Cha, you will understand
when you become a parent.
So please be generous and forgive me.
Forgive me, okay?
Bye.
I'll see you again.
- I'll see you, okay?
- Okay.
So please be generous and forgive me.
Forgive me, okay?
Seo-kyeong.
- Seo-kyeong.
- Yeah?
- Should I just forgive her?
- Huh?
That pretty lady.
Should we forgive her?
Yeah.
Uncle, drink this.
What is it?
The lady brought it.
She said to give it to you.
Mushroom tea and honey or something?
I'll drink it.
Mom! This is Uncle's medicine!
Okay. You drink it, Uncle.
She said it's medicine?
Yes, she said it's good for your heart.
Is your heart sick, Uncle?
No.
I heard you're pretty sick, Mr. Cha.
Be sure to take three tablets a day.
Where is the X-ray film that was here?
X-ray film?
Yeah, the one that looked like a skull.
My X-ray!
Choi Yun took it the other day.
What?
My Yun is the only blood descendant I have.
Transplant? Do you mean a heart transplant?
When a mother is blinded by her child,
she can't see the difference between right and wrong.
I know. I'll be punished.
I will be punished.
If God forgets to punish me,
make sure you punish me.
When you get healthy enough to defeat
anyone who messes with you, son,
make sure you punish me.
I know.
My sins. I'll be punished them for all.
Son.
Open the door!
What is this noise?
Is that our door?
Who is that? Yun and his mom aren't even home.
Honey. Honey!
Will you go and see? It's probably some drunk lunatic.
Open the door!
Is this what you wanted?
You wanted my heart?
I...
I'm your son, too.
Just like Yun.
You gave birth to me.
You brought me into this world.
I'm your bloodline, too!
I'm your son, too.
I'm your son!
I'm your son, too!
You're okay...
You're okay.
Mister. What are you doing here?
You're going to freeze to death.
Even if...
Even if things with Yun don't go as planned,
I won't go to you.
I'm never going to be with you. Never.
So go. Go to wherever you belong.
We can meet in the next life.
You and I...
Weren't meant to be this time around.
Let's meet in the next life.
In the next life, I won't let you go. No matter what.
What do you want?
I'm a busy person.
I didn't come here to watch you work out.
I have a question.
Were you...
Were you serious about Eunchae?
Not the way you liked me.
You really liked Eunchae, didn't you?
That's some talent. Mr. Cha Muhyeok.
How can you make the great Kang Minju
feel so miserable?
I really don't want to let you go.
Help! My arms! Mr. Song.
What's this?
Kimchi for Galchi's.
Mr. Song! What a waste!
What were you thinking?
Stop it.
What?
Stop it, Audrey.
Mr. Song.
Don't go there ever again.
You're definitely going to pay for it, if you do.
It's not what you think.
I'm doing it, truly out of the goodness of my heart.
For Seo-kyeong, Galchi, and Muhyeok.
Because I like them. I feel for them. I really do.
Just stop it, please!
How far are you going to take it?
How far are you going to go?
Is your son's life the only life
you think is important?
Mr. Cha's life is just as valuable to his parents!
I told you! It's not what you think!
I really do feel for them!
Like they're my own children!
At least Yun has hope. Muhyeok has nothing.
They said he has no chance of living.
He's just waiting to die.
Yun has you, doing everything you can to save him.
Muhyeok has no one!
He has a slow sister who wouldn't
even understand the concept of death
and a little nephew he needs to take care of!
Just leave Muhyeok alone, please.
Let him live what's left of his life, in peace.
Are you going to die for sure, Mister?
When are you dying, Mister?
Maximum three months. Minimum...
[Episode 13 Preview]
What's wrong?
[Her tears are my death]
Let's go inside and rub some medicine on it.
Are you hurt anywhere else?
You should be more careful, dummy!
Let go.
I'm fine. I'm fine.